<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>1985</Date_of_birth
><Name
>Grimlock</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>12,6 m</Height
><Weight
>24 ton</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>5W-30</Blood_type
><Rank
>Lead Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>A</Security_level
><Signature
>Grimlock</Signature
><Date
>23.8.2022</Date
><Employee_code xfdf:original="Employee code"
>ITXX-02</Employee_code
><Department
>System Center Department</Department
><Background
>Grimlock is an ego-maniacal, impatient and willful Autobot. As he's more than willing to disobey any direct order if he thinks that the ends will justify his means. He gets anger issues if anyone dares to tick him off, they're scrap. Despite that, he is loyal to the Autobot cause and is willing to risk his life to rescue his comrades from capture. During Shockwave's experimentation on him, Grimlock gained a new "Alt Mode", making him more aggressive than ever. Grimlock's speech patterns hide's a surprisingly intelligent mind. Grimlock is known for not following orders or trusting in Optimus Prime's ability to be an effective leader. As the leader of the Lightning Strike Coalition Force, Grimlock enjoys smashing things first and asking questions later. Due to Shockwave's experiments, Grimlock has been left with a malfunctioning voice processor and an alt-mode inspired by a distant primitive world.</Background
><Strengths
>Physically, Grimlock is one of the strongest Cybertronians alive, he has accomplished amazing feats using his berserk, monstrous strength, he has pushed down towers with ease, break through steel walls, single-handedly took down an army of Decepticons, was able to go one-on-one with Megatron, smash boulders with his bare hands. There are some rumors that Grimlock's strength is limitless, he might even overpower Unicron, his rage also fuels him with might, the angrier he becomes, the stronger he gets. He is also equipped with an Energy Sword (Flame Swords in different media). In his Dinobot/T-Rex Mode, Grimlock's strength is somewhat stronger than his Cybertronian Form, his jaws are so powerful, he can bite through virtually anything (unknown if he can actually bite through the apex armor), Grimlock can also eat Decepticons up (though it does not power him up like Chompazoids do). His T-Rex mode also has the ability to breath fire, the fire that Grimlock breathes is so hot, it can burn buildings from miles away, this flame can also burn Decepticons down.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>His lack of fear makes him a dangerous foe, he loves to fight, often he starts one, he isn't afraid to fight either Bruticus or Devastator. But his berserk-like anger makes him too dangerous to other Autobots as well, (as stated by some Autobots that "In the battlefield, better fear Grimlock than the hoard of Decepticons around you").</Weaknesses
></fields>