<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>31.10.1958</Date_of_birth
><Name
>Gargamel</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>187 cm</Height
><Weight
>65 kg</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>RED</Blood_type
><Rank
>Lead Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>A</Security_level
><Signature
>Gargamel</Signature
><Date
>23.8.2022</Date
><Employee_code xfdf:original="Employee code"
>ITXX-05</Employee_code
><Department
>System Center Department</Department
><Background
>Unlike his cartoon show counterpart, his first encounter with the Smurfs was five years prior to Empath's final return to the Smurf Village, when Gargamel sought to capture a Smurf to complete the formula for the creation of the Philosopher's Stone. The Smurfs, after finding out from Brainy Smurf that Nabby was the Smurf captured by Gargamel, had staked out the wizard's castle in order to find a way to break Nabby out of his cage before sunrise. However, as all the Smurfs' attempts to free Nabby before that time came to nothing, they resorted to attacking Gargamel directly until he fell unconscious, allowing them to escape to the village with Nabby. Gargamel, upon awakening, tried to use a formula that he thought would turn him into a giant in order to find the Smurfs, but instead the formula shrank him to Smurf-size, making him realize that the Smurfs had switched the contents of his bottles.</Background
><Strengths
>Gargamel is a very competent if not masterful sorcerer and alchemist who is fully capable of creating all sorts of inventions for capturing and potentially destroying Smurfs. For inventions that are beyond his own abilities to create, he usually turns to the Great Book Of Spells for assistance, though it rarely gives him exactly what he wants, nor does what he gets ever works out in his favor.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Gargamel is usually done in by the very inventions and spells that he uses against the Smurfs. He is also rather powerless against the mindlink that Empath uses in conjunction with the Smurfs against him. </Weaknesses
></fields>